[
	{
		"question": "Похоронен",
		"answer": "Buried"
	},
	{
		"question": "Я закрыл шторы",
		"answer": "I cloused the curtains"
	},
	{
		"question": "Я влючил весь свет в доме",
		"answer": "I turned on every light in the house"
	},
	{
		"question": "Я положил больше углей в огонь",
		"answer": "I put more coal in the fire"
	},
	{
		"question": "Я пошел наверх",
		"answer": "I went upstairs"
	},
	{
		"question": "Полчаса",
		"answer": "Half of hour"
	},
	{
		"question": "Просыпаться",
		"answer": "Wake up"
	},
	{
		"question": "Рычать",
		"answer": "Growl"
	},
	{
		"question": "Проход",
		"answer": "Passage"
	},
	{
		"question": "Нюхать",
		"answer": "Sniffed"
	},
	{
		"question": "Медленно, я начал идти по направлению звука",
		"answer": "Slowly, I began to walk torwards the sound"
	},
	{
		"question": "Мы оба тряслись от страха",
		"answer": "We were both shaking with fear"
	},
	{
		"question": "Я почувствовал что-то теплое прижалось к моей ноге",
		"answer": "I felt something warm against my let"
	},
	{
		"question": "Однако",
		"answer": "However"
	},
	{
		"question": "Я работал усердно несколько часов",
		"answer": "I worked hard for several hours"
	},
	{
		"question": "Рядом",
		"answer": "Beside"
	},
	{
		"question": "Во рту пересохло от страха",
		"answer": "My mouth was dry with fear"
	},
	{
		"question": "Пыль",
		"answer": "Dust"
	},
	{
		"question": "Рука",
		"answer": "Arm"
	},
	{
		"question": "Проход",
		"answer": "Passage"
	},
	{
		"question": "Мои пальцы",
		"answer": "My fingers"
	},
	{
		"question": "Я зажег свечу",
		"answer": "I lit the candle"
	},
	{
		"question": "Некоторе время спустя, я уснул",
		"answer": "Some time later, I fell asleep"
	},
	{
		"question": "Что со мной случилось?",
		"answer": "What happened to me?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Мы рядом с этим местом?",
		"answer": "Are we near this place?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Этого платежа достаточно?",
		"answer": "Is this payment enough?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Этот мальчик его старший брат?",
		"answer": "It this boy his elder brother?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Эта еда вкусная?",
		"answer": "Is this food delicious?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Эта еда очень вкусная?",
		"answer": "Is this food very testy?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Все студенты знают значение этого выражения?",
		"answer": "Do all the students know the meaning of this expression?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Какое значение этого слова?",
		"answer": "What's the meaning of this word?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Что это слово значит?",
		"answer": "What does this word mean?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Что ты имеешь в виду?",
		"answer": "What do you mean?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Я думаю, что ты идиот",
		"answer": "I think that you idiot"
	},
	{
		"question": "Тебе нужно сделать это в следующем году?",
		"answer": "Do you need to do it next year?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Тебе нужно закончить это к завтрашнему дню?",
		"answer": "Do you need to finish it by tomorrow?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Ты знаешь каждого?",
		"answer": "Do you know each other?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Они живут раздельно",
		"answer": "They live separatly"
	},
	{
		"question": "Она устала",
		"answer": "She's tired"
	},
	{
		"question": "Они боятся",
		"answer": "They're afraid"
	},
	{
		"question": "Я увлекаюсь программированием",
		"answer": "I'm keen on programming"
	},
	{
		"question": "Это интересует его?",
		"answer": "Does it inserest him?"
	},
	{
		"question": "Это интересует его",
		"answer": "It inserests him"
	},
	{
		"question": "Это удобное время",
		"answer": "This time is convenient"
	}
]
